All right!
Ew.
The picture of vanity.
We have a narcissist here.
Chinatsu.
A morning shampoo and shower,
and to top it off, posing
in front of the mirror.
How vain could you be?
I'm not vain! I'm just setting
an example for myself!
How can you eat junk food
so early in the morning?
Want some?
Never!
Okay.
Jeez... I told you not to come
into my room without permission.
So cold! How could you forget our sibling bond
just because we were living apart?
I made a decision
that I would never return to the days
when I was so naïve and powerless.
Good morning, Maa-kun, Chinatsu-chan.
Breakfast is ready.
Milk
You loved donuts when you were
little, didn't you, Maa-kun?
High in Calories
They're loaded with sugar!
The fried chicken's fresh out of the fryer, too.
Can't you hear them sizzling?
Er, no thanks...
Chinatsu!
Maa-kun just said he hates his mommy!
And when we're finally able
to live together again!
Yeah, yeah. Seems like Onii-chan
got rid of a lot of baggage.
I'm heading out.
Maa-kun!
Like I could eat something that high
in calories so early in the morning.
"Everything depends on
whether you're hot or not."
This is my motto.
If you're not a hot guy, you're not human.
Even a normal guy attains
birth in the Pure Land,
so it goes without saying that a hot guy will.
Hey, what are you gawking at?
Let me see your cell phone!
You've got the wrong idea!
I was just sending a text!
You're lying. No one holds a
phone that way to type a text!
Seriously, it's not what you think!
Then hurry up and let me see your phone!
My sin should be much
worse than that poor fool
Yeah!
who took out his cell phone
without thinking.
Wait, are you Makabe Masamune-kun?
Y-Yes...
I knew it!
Who's that?
Makabe-kun. He transferred here last week.
Oh, are you interested in tennis?
Would you like to practice with us?
Er, no...
Did you really get a perfect
score on the transfer exam?
Wow!
I saw you playing soccer! You looked so cool!
Oh, man... Could this be...
You're too kind. I was
actually admiring how hard
all of you were practicing.
Well, keep up the good work.
So cool!
I'm in love!
"Everything depends on whether
you're hot or not"... I guess it's true.
My plan may work after all!
Shigeo-senpai is going to confess his love?
To the Cruel Princess?
I bet she'll finally break this time.
I know she's the Cruel Princess and all,
but Shigeo-senpai is a super hot guy.
She's here!
You came, my bashful little Rapunzel!
There's no need to be shy.
I'm used to people staring at me.
That's why I want your answer,
right here, right now.
Well, that's good, then.
Yamada Shigeo-senpai from class 3-C,
What's going on?
thank you very much for asking me out.
A public confession of love?
Because of this, I had one of my servants
run a background check on you.
Huh?
As a result, I see that...
you recently went to the bookstore by
the station to buy the new volume of
"Oh, Jeez! I'm Ryuubi Gentoku in a
Genderswapped 'Romance of the Three Kingdoms'"
and then hid it in a college workbook.
"Genderswapped"?
Also, I don't think unnaturally staring at
an underclassman's upper arm flab
is a very favorable hobby.
I also wonder about your internet-serialized
empowerment-fantasy novel
whose protagonist shares your name, "Shigeo."
W-Wait...
I can explain...
You've got it all wrong!
And you always have
a single hair growing from
the mole on your chest.
From the bottom of my heart,
I grant you this name.
Moleo
Moleo...
And I really liked Yamada-kun, too.
But if he's "Moleo"...
That's the Cruel Princess for you.
She's merciless.
The city is scary... The city is scary...
No... I can't lose my nerve
over something like this.
My battle's just begu—
#1 "The Boy Who Was Called Pig's Foot"
I'll never fall in love with you.
No...
You're just...
No!
C-Crap! I totally let my guard down!
Hey, Makabe! You're slacking off!
Right! I'm sorry!
Er, huh?
Good morning, Makabe-kun.
You were sound asleep.
Oh, it's you, Class Rep Futaba.
But that just means you're
finally adjusting to this school.
As the class rep, I feel relieved.
Hot guys can get away with sleeping
in class, and even drooling?
Oh, Makabe-kun's awake.
Sh-Shuri-kun.
You can just call me Kojuurou.
You haven't had lunch yet, right?
If you go now, the school store
will just be sold out, so...
O-Oh, thanks. You're a lifesaver.
This bread has a full meal's
worth of calories...
A Man's Yakisoba Bread
Spicy!!
Not to mention it's mostly carbs!
I'll have to do an extra hundred
crunches when I get home.
You're amazing, Makabe-kun. You get good
grades, but don't act stuck up at all.
You're good at sports, too.
And you're good-looking!
Oh, stop.
And I hear you're quite popular
with a certain crowd
that calls you "Kojuurou-kyun,
the designated bottom."
There is one other person who's as
highly accomplished as you, but...
Oh, you mean that one?
"That one"?
Yeah, the one who...
Is Tanabe Akio here?
That's the girl from this morning...
You'll do just fine. Answer me.
Is Tanabe Akio here or not?
Um, uh...
Th-That's me.
"I fell for how dignified you look in PE class."
Simply put, you like how
my legs look in shorts.
From now on, I'll call you "Pudding Prince."
Let's go, Yoshino.
Wh-What's with her?
She has the best grades in our
year and is really beautiful,
but her personality is nothing
like yours, Makabe-kun.
On top of that, she really hates guys
and gives anyone who asks her out
Yikes... You okay?
cruel nicknames and drives them off.
Hang in there.
That's why they call her the "Cruel Princess."
Her name is Adagaki Aki-san.
She's the daughter of the
head of the Adagaki Group.
Adagaki...?
Makabe-kun?
What's the matter?
Adagaki Aki...
That's her?
Who would've thought
I'd run into her again so soon?
Aki-sama, would you like another cup of tea?
Thank you. I would.
These are chocolates I ordered
from a chocolatier in Brussels.
Please, try one.
How lovely. But I'm going to pass for now.
It looks like what Kojuurou
told me was correct,
but she seems to have a lot
of girls as her lackeys.
Oh, Sonoka. Your ribbon's coming loose.
Aki-sama...
I thought she'd be feared by girls, too,
but I guess that's not the case.
Apparently some girls think she's
cool because she's so blunt.
Is that how it works?
But the one who's always with her is
Koiwai Yoshino-san.
Anything else?
Yeah, like her type, her likes
and dislikes, or her tendencies.
I'm not sure. I can't say
I've heard much about that.
I think the only thing I've heard is
that she likes to eat lunch alone.
If you'll excuse me.
Farewell, Aki-sama.
Farewell.
Bye-bye, Aki-sama.
Huh...
So she's usually in a harem situation
with all these girls waiting on her,
but that's not the case when she's eating.
I'm going to have to look into this.
I wouldn't do that, Makabe-kun.
She'll probably do something awful to you.
I won't have to worry about
that! I don't think.
You think so?
Oh, crap.
I wonder what's up with Makabe-kun.
I messed up.
Where did
she go?
Now that I actually want to find her,
I realize this school is huge.
That's...
There's no doubt about it.
That's one of Adagaki Aki's lackeys.
I definitely remember that unfortunate aura.
Something seems fishy...
What could she be doing there?
I bought them.
What took you so long, Yoshino?
I got tired of waiting.
Sorry, but there were only
two cutlet sandwiches.
Then you could have just
bought something else.
Have you no sense?
Bingo! I've found you, Adagaki Aki!
What's that metal case?
A spider!
Heya.
Sorry, I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
I just happened to see her walk in here.
Are you saying that you
didn't think I'd be in here?
Right.
Who the hell would expect to
find the great Adagaki Aki
eating alone in the gym storage room?
And the idea that she loves
high-calorie meals that are
ideal for people who do physical labor...
High in Calories
You're in the way, so would you mind leaving?
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure there are some athletic girls who
eat slightly bigger lunches like that.
Heck, my little sister...
Would you like your bread now?
Later is fine.
I-I can't help it!
If I just eat like everyone else,
I get hungry again right away.
I'm prone to hypoglycemia, so I always
have to make sure I get enough sugar.
I thought I seriously might have
a parasite, so I had tests done,
but they didn't find anything.
Anyway, I have to do everything I can to
make sure my stomach doesn't rumble.
You don't hear a normal girl's
stomach rumbling, ever!
Or what? Do you want my stomach
making noises as loud as Big Ben?
Is that what you're into?!
O-Oh, yeah... I just remembered
somewhere I have to be.
What's your name?
Makabe.
Tell anyone about this, and you'll regret it.
But I've just been dealt a trump card!
Makabe-kun, I hear you're
friendly with Adagaki-san now.
Where did that come from?
That's the rumor in our class. Whoa, whoa...
Everyone thinks the Cruel Princess
might finally fall this time.
Oh, man...
It's not like that at all.
In reality, she's only been
mean to me ever since.
Are they that delusional?
Girls are scary when it comes to love.
Someone that pretty is able
to eat that super hefty meal.
No one would believe that... right?
Back to Your Dog House
What am I, a dog?!
Ow!
A-Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Are you okay? Do you need
to go to the nurse's office?
No, I'm fine.
Don't get full of yourself.
Makabe-kun, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I guess it's not only girls who are
like that when it comes to love.
That's really annoying, but I
can use that to my advantage.
Hours of Operation
Open Year-Round
Farewell, Aki-sama.
See you tomorrow.
Bye-bye!
Farewell!
Yoshino.
Yoshino, wake up!
I'm so hungry that I might faint.
Go buy me something to eat.
Right now?
Yes. Hurry.
What would you like?
Something with rice, or bread?
I told you, I'm about to faint.
It doesn't matter what it is.
Just hurry up and go buy it.
Right.
I ate a proper lunch.
It seems my body's calorie
consumption is getting worse...
How far did Yoshino go, anyway?
You're in quite a hurry.
Do you have a date with Makabe?
You're the Pudding Pr—
Shut up!
Oh, but it's such a fitting nickname.
You don't like—
You ripped up my letter,
but Makabe's just fine?
Must be nice to be a hot guy.
Looks don't matter. Let go of me.
You think you're such a princess,
looking down on everyone else!
Don't!
I always thought something like
this might happen eventually.
Because you're so scary, Adagaki-san.
Are you hurt?
Th-That's what I should be asking you.
This is nothing, as long as you're safe.
O—
Ow!
Ow, ow! That seriously hurt, damn it!
It so hurts! It frickin' hurts!
I want to cry! I want to scream!
Actually, can I just pass out?
But now...
I bet she can't be nasty to me anymore.
Not only do I know Adagaki Aki's secret,
but now I've saved her.
Her pride won't let her get away with that.
Don't make that face.
Girls are much cuter when they're smiling.
M-My daddy's super rich!
Let me make a confession. I was a fatty.
On top of that, I was a snobby
rich kid and a target of bullies.
What are you all doing in front of my house?
Back then, Adagaki Aki looked like
a savior to me.
Until that fateful moment...
I won't fall for you.
You're just a Pig's Foot!
This is revenge, Adagaki Aki.
I hate you and despise you
so much that I can't bear it.
That's why I'm going to do whatever it takes
to make you fall in love with me now.
And when she really does, it'll all be over.
I'll tell her who I am, then dump her
in the most awesome way possible.
I call it the "Dead or Love Plan."
Oh, Maa-kun seems to be in a good mood.
Gross.
Good morning, Makabe-kun.
Morning.
Good morning, Futaba-san.
What happened to your hand?
Oh, I was just a bit clumsy.
I didn't know you could be clumsy,
Makabe-kun. How surprising.
That sexy contrast between hot
and clumsy! Score one for me!
Good morning, Tanabe-kun.
G-Good morning...
Sorry about yesterday.
Hey, it's all good. Don't worry about it.
Huh? What? What happened?
It's a secret.
Good morning, Makabe-kun.
Morning.
Wow, a love letter? Nice.
Oh, I'm not sure about that...
Pig's Foot
Huh?
Could it be...
I've already been found out?